Resume

My name is Gabriel de Rezende Gonçalves, Brazilian. I am 21 years old, live in Campinas/SP, am a computer technician, attending the eighth semester in Software Engineering at the Pontifical Catholic University of Campinas, and intern at Encora.

Contact

Email: contato@gabireze.com.br LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/gabireze

Site: gabireze.com.br

GitHub: github.com/gabireze

Experiences

Software Engineering Intern at Encora

February 2021 – Current

Supervised monitoring of systems development; Supervised monitoring of reporting; Supervised monitoring in the maintenance of systems or programs; Participated in technical and behavioral training

Student Exchange Program at Canadian College of English Language - CCEL

July 2022 - Vancouver, Canada

English 125 (English Level B2 - Upper Intermediate); 38 weekly classes; Basic Class + 2 Electives.

Software Engineering Intern at SuperOpa and OpaBox

June 2019 - January 2021

Fullstack development in Flutter and Javascript based on software componentization using microservices and scalable solutions for APIs, development of resources available from RESTful Web Services, use of Vue.js as a Javascript framework, and Node.js as a server-side Javascript execution environment. Experience with Agile methodologies (SCRUM and Kanban), use of Git for version control, Slack for communication between collaborators, and project management by Jira and Trello. I am implementing tests on APIs or Webservices using Postman, used to the Serverless Architecture provided by AWS (S3, DynamoDB, CloudFront, API Gateway, CloudWatch, SQS).

Academic education

Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Campinas

Bachelor's Degree, Software Engineering

2019 - 2022

ETEC Bento Quirino

Integrated Technician to High School, IT

2016 - 2018

Languages

English - Upper-Intermediate

Spanish - Technical / Basic

Portuguese - Fluent / Native

Technical abilities

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Dart, C, Java, PHP
- React, Flutter, Vue.js, AngularJS, Bootstrap
- Node.js, Express.js, Serverless Framework
- MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL
- npm, Git, Swagger, Docker, Jira, Trello, Figma, Postman, Slack, SCRUM, Kanban
- Visual Studio Code, Android Studio, Linux, macOS, Windows
- Firebase, AWS, Amazon DynamoDB, AWS Lambda, S3, CloudFront, API Gateway, CloudWatch, SQS

Interpersonal skills

- Creativity, Persuasion, Collaboration, Adaptability, Time Management
- Organization of groups, Negotiation of solutions, Empathy, Social Sensitivity
- Emotional self-awareness, Emotional control, Self-motivation
- Recognition of emotions in other people, Skill in interpersonal relationships